thecashchat.com 2015-04-06

# Privacy Policy - The Cash Chat Forum - Sponsored by EarningPalace.com

## **The Cash Chat Forum is for Sale interested may contact me at   ****"admin[@]thecashchat.com"**

[ Advertise ](http://thecashchat.com/forum/cp/1-advertise/ "Advertise on Thecashchat.Com")your 728*90 px banner Here @ $249 Per Month

(All the banners and links are [advertisements](http://thecashchat.com/forum/cp/2-advertising-disclaimer/ "Thecashchat Forum advertisement disclaimer") only. TCC dose not endorse or vouch for any advertisers.)

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Cookies**  
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties. 

  1.  
  2. [Privacy Policy](http://thecashchat.com/forum/privacypolicy/)
